[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the main gas responsible for the greenhouse effect?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Methane"],
    "answer": "Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What percentage of the Earth's surface is covered by oceans?",
    "choices": ["About 50%", "About 71%", "About 60%", "About 80%"],
    "answer": "About 71%"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which layer of Earth's atmosphere contains the ozone layer?",
    "choices": ["Troposphere", "Stratosphere", "Mesosphere", "Thermosphere"],
    "answer": "Stratosphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the process plants use to convert sunlight into food?",
    "choices": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Respiration",
      "Transpiration",
      "Fermentation"
    ],
    "answer": "Photosynthesis"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the largest source of renewable energy in the world?",
    "choices": [
      "Solar Energy",
      "Wind Energy",
      "Hydropower",
      "Geothermal Energy"
    ],
    "answer": "Hydropower"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the most abundant gas in Earth's atmosphere?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Argon"],
    "answer": "Nitrogen"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What type of energy is produced by the sun?",
    "choices": [
      "Thermal Energy",
      "Nuclear Energy",
      "Solar Energy",
      "Radiant Energy"
    ],
    "answer": "Solar Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which country produces the most wind energy?",
    "choices": ["United States", "China", "Germany", "India"],
    "answer": "China"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the primary cause of global warming?",
    "choices": [
      "Natural Sun Cycles",
      "Deforestation",
      "Greenhouse Gases",
      "Volcanic Eruptions"
    ],
    "answer": "Greenhouse Gases"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which gas is released during the burning of fossil fuels?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Helium"],
    "answer": "Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What does the term 'biodiversity' refer to?",
    "choices": [
      "Variety of food crops",
      "Different climates on Earth",
      "Variety of life on Earth",
      "Variety of water bodies"
    ],
    "answer": "Variety of life on Earth"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the main cause of the depletion of the ozone layer?",
    "choices": [
      "Greenhouse Gases",
      "Chlorofluorocarbons",
      "Carbon Monoxide",
      "Methane"
    ],
    "answer": "Chlorofluorocarbons"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which is not a renewable resource?",
    "choices": ["Solar energy", "Wind energy", "Coal", "Hydropower"],
    "answer": "Coal"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What is the most common form of waste found in oceans?",
    "choices": ["Plastic", "Glass", "Metal", "Rubber"],
    "answer": "Plastic"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is deforestation?",
    "choices": [
      "Planting more trees",
      "Clearing of forests",
      "Urbanization",
      "Desertification"
    ],
    "answer": "Clearing of forests"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Which renewable energy source uses the Earth's heat?",
    "choices": [
      "Solar Energy",
      "Wind Energy",
      "Geothermal Energy",
      "Hydropower"
    ],
    "answer": "Geothermal Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What percentage of the world's water is fresh and readily accessible?",
    "choices": ["Less than 1%", "About 10%", "About 3%", "About 20%"],
    "answer": "Less than 1%"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is the primary gas found in natural gas?",
    "choices": ["Carbon Dioxide", "Methane", "Nitrogen", "Oxygen"],
    "answer": "Methane"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What term describes the variety of habitats, species, and genes in an ecosystem?",
    "choices": ["Ecology", "Biodiversity", "Ecosystem", "Biome"],
    "answer": "Biodiversity"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Which gas is primarily responsible for acid rain?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Monoxide", "Sulfur Dioxide", "Nitrogen"],
    "answer": "Sulfur Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What is the term for the cultivation of aquatic plants and animals for food?",
    "choices": ["Aquaculture", "Hydroponics", "Mariculture", "Fishery"],
    "answer": "Aquaculture"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What is the main cause of ocean acidification?",
    "choices": [
      "Oil Spills",
      "Increased Salinity",
      "Absorption of Carbon Dioxide",
      "Overfishing"
    ],
    "answer": "Absorption of Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What process involves the conversion of waste into usable energy?",
    "choices": ["Recycling", "Composting", "Waste-to-Energy", "Landfilling"],
    "answer": "Waste-to-Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What type of forest is characterized by high rainfall and year-round warmth?",
    "choices": [
      "Temperate Forest",
      "Rainforest",
      "Boreal Forest",
      "Deciduous Forest"
    ],
    "answer": "Rainforest"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What is the primary cause of soil erosion?",
    "choices": [
      "Deforestation",
      "Pesticide Use",
      "Urbanization",
      "Overgrazing"
    ],
    "answer": "Deforestation"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Which layer of soil is most fertile and rich in organic matter?",
    "choices": ["Bedrock", "Subsoil", "Topsoil", "Parent Material"],
    "answer": "Topsoil"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What term refers to the maximum number of individuals an environment can support without degradation?",
    "choices": [
      "Carrying Capacity",
      "Population Density",
      "Ecological Footprint",
      "Biotic Potential"
    ],
    "answer": "Carrying Capacity"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What renewable energy source is derived from organic materials like plant and animal waste?",
    "choices": ["Solar Energy", "Biomass Energy", "Hydropower", "Wind Energy"],
    "answer": "Biomass Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What is the process by which water vapor turns into liquid water?",
    "choices": [
      "Evaporation",
      "Condensation",
      "Precipitation",
      "Transpiration"
    ],
    "answer": "Condensation"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What phenomenon is causing the rise in sea levels?",
    "choices": [
      "Tectonic Activity",
      "Global Warming",
      "Lunar Gravitational Pull",
      "Ocean Currents"
    ],
    "answer": "Global Warming"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "Which continent is most affected by desertification?",
    "choices": ["Asia", "Africa", "Australia", "North America"],
    "answer": "Africa"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "What is the main environmental benefit of reforestation?",
    "choices": [
      "Increasing Agricultural Land",
      "Reducing Soil Erosion",
      "Improving Air Quality",
      "Enhancing Aesthetic Value"
    ],
    "answer": "Reducing Soil Erosion"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "What is the term for a community of organisms and their physical environment interacting together?",
    "choices": ["Biome", "Ecosystem", "Habitat", "Biosphere"],
    "answer": "Ecosystem"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Which type of pollution is caused by light being scattered and reflected?",
    "choices": [
      "Air Pollution",
      "Noise Pollution",
      "Water Pollution",
      "Light Pollution"
    ],
    "answer": "Light Pollution"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "What process is used to remove salt from seawater to make it suitable for drinking and irrigation?",
    "choices": ["Filtration", "Desalination", "Chlorination", "Distillation"],
    "answer": "Desalination"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Which term describes the loss of water from the soil due to evaporation and transpiration by plants?",
    "choices": ["Percolation", "Infiltration", "Runoff", "Evapotranspiration"],
    "answer": "Evapotranspiration"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "What is the primary method for sustainable waste management?",
    "choices": ["Incineration", "Landfilling", "Recycling", "Composting"],
    "answer": "Recycling"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "What natural phenomenon is used in generating tidal energy?",
    "choices": ["Sun's Heat", "Wind", "Ocean Tides", "River Currents"],
    "answer": "Ocean Tides"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "What is the study of how organisms interact with each other and their environment?",
    "choices": ["Geology", "Meteorology", "Ecology", "Botany"],
    "answer": "Ecology"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "Which renewable energy source primarily relies on flowing water?",
    "choices": ["Solar Energy", "Wind Energy", "Hydropower", "Biomass Energy"],
    "answer": "Hydropower"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "What term describes the gradual increase in the Earth's temperature?",
    "choices": [
      "Global Cooling",
      "Global Warming",
      "Climate Change",
      "Seasonal Shift"
    ],
    "answer": "Global Warming"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "What is the primary greenhouse gas emitted through human activities?",
    "choices": ["Methane", "Nitrous Oxide", "Carbon Dioxide", "Ozone"],
    "answer": "Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "What is the main cause of rising sea levels?",
    "choices": [
      "Glacial Melting",
      "Underwater Volcanoes",
      "Coral Reef Decay",
      "Increased Sedimentation"
    ],
    "answer": "Glacial Melting"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "What type of energy is harnessed from the sun's rays?",
    "choices": [
      "Thermal Energy",
      "Geothermal Energy",
      "Solar Energy",
      "Nuclear Energy"
    ],
    "answer": "Solar Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "What process involves planting trees to restore a forest?",
    "choices": [
      "Afforestation",
      "Deforestation",
      "Reforestation",
      "Urbanization"
    ],
    "answer": "Reforestation"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "Which layer of Earth's atmosphere is closest to the surface?",
    "choices": ["Stratosphere", "Troposphere", "Mesosphere", "Exosphere"],
    "answer": "Troposphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "What phenomenon is characterized by the spinning of the Earth on its axis?",
    "choices": ["Orbit", "Revolution", "Rotation", "Eclipse"],
    "answer": "Rotation"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "What is the primary cause of desertification?",
    "choices": [
      "Heavy Rainfall",
      "Forest Fires",
      "Overgrazing",
      "Frequent Flooding"
    ],
    "answer": "Overgrazing"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "Which gas is most responsible for trapping heat in the atmosphere?",
    "choices": ["Carbon Dioxide", "Methane", "Oxygen", "Nitrogen"],
    "answer": "Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "What term refers to the variety of different types of organisms in a habitat or region?",
    "choices": [
      "Ecosystem Diversity",
      "Species Diversity",
      "Genetic Diversity",
      "Biodiversity"
    ],
    "answer": "Biodiversity"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "What type of pollution occurs when harmful substances enter the soil?",
    "choices": [
      "Air Pollution",
      "Soil Pollution",
      "Water Pollution",
      "Noise Pollution"
    ],
    "answer": "Soil Pollution"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "Which gas is a major component of smog?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Monoxide", "Nitrogen Dioxide", "Methane"],
    "answer": "Nitrogen Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "What is the main driver of ocean currents?",
    "choices": [
      "Marine Life",
      "Moon's Gravitational Pull",
      "Wind Patterns",
      "Thermal Energy from the Sun"
    ],
    "answer": "Wind Patterns"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "What process is crucial for the water cycle, involving the transition from liquid to gas?",
    "choices": ["Condensation", "Evaporation", "Precipitation", "Infiltration"],
    "answer": "Evaporation"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "What is the primary method of reducing greenhouse gases in the atmosphere?",
    "choices": [
      "Fossil Fuel Consumption",
      "Deforestation",
      "Carbon Sequestration",
      "Urbanization"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon Sequestration"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "Which phenomenon is directly related to the depletion of fish stocks in the ocean?",
    "choices": [
      "Global Warming",
      "Coral Bleaching",
      "Overfishing",
      "Marine Pollution"
    ],
    "answer": "Overfishing"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "What term is used to describe the breaking down of organic material in the absence of oxygen?",
    "choices": [
      "Composting",
      "Fermentation",
      "Anaerobic Digestion",
      "Photosynthesis"
    ],
    "answer": "Anaerobic Digestion"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "Which energy source relies on the heat generated by the natural decay of radioactive materials?",
    "choices": [
      "Solar Energy",
      "Wind Energy",
      "Geothermal Energy",
      "Hydropower"
    ],
    "answer": "Geothermal Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "What is the main effect of thermal pollution on aquatic ecosystems?",
    "choices": [
      "Decreased Oxygen Levels",
      "Increased Salinity",
      "Algal Blooms",
      "Acidification"
    ],
    "answer": "Decreased Oxygen Levels"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "What is the primary cause of coral bleaching?",
    "choices": [
      "Overfishing",
      "Oil Spills",
      "Increased Sea Temperature",
      "Plastic Pollution"
    ],
    "answer": "Increased Sea Temperature"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "What term describes the change in the statistical distribution of weather patterns over periods of time?",
    "choices": [
      "Weather Fluctuation",
      "Climate Change",
      "Global Warming",
      "Seasonal Variation"
    ],
    "answer": "Climate Change"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "question": "What is the process of water movement through a plant and its evaporation from aerial parts?",
    "choices": [
      "Transpiration",
      "Respiration",
      "Condensation",
      "Photosynthesis"
    ],
    "answer": "Transpiration"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "question": "Which gas is used as a reference to measure the global warming potential of other greenhouse gases?",
    "choices": ["Carbon Dioxide", "Methane", "Nitrous Oxide", "Ozone"],
    "answer": "Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "question": "What type of energy production relies on harnessing wind power using turbines?",
    "choices": ["Solar Energy", "Wind Energy", "Hydropower", "Nuclear Energy"],
    "answer": "Wind Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "question": "Which layer of the earth is composed of tectonic plates?",
    "choices": ["Crust", "Mantle", "Core", "Lithosphere"],
    "answer": "Lithosphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "question": "What phenomenon results in the reduction of land's ability to support life, often due to human activity?",
    "choices": [
      "Erosion",
      "Land Degradation",
      "Desertification",
      "Deforestation"
    ],
    "answer": "Land Degradation"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "question": "What is the main environmental impact of using fossil fuels?",
    "choices": [
      "Biodiversity Loss",
      "Air Pollution",
      "Soil Fertility Increase",
      "Water Conservation"
    ],
    "answer": "Air Pollution"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "question": "Which type of renewable energy is obtained from the movement of water, such as in rivers or tides?",
    "choices": ["Solar Energy", "Wind Energy", "Hydropower", "Biomass Energy"],
    "answer": "Hydropower"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "question": "What is the term for the layer of gases that surrounds the Earth?",
    "choices": ["Biosphere", "Atmosphere", "Hydrosphere", "Lithosphere"],
    "answer": "Atmosphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "What process removes carbon dioxide from the atmosphere and stores it in plants and soil?",
    "choices": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Carbon Sequestration",
      "Respiration",
      "Transpiration"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon Sequestration"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "question": "What is the primary driver of the greenhouse effect?",
    "choices": [
      "Solar Radiation",
      "Greenhouse Gases",
      "Methane Emissions",
      "Ozone Depletion"
    ],
    "answer": "Greenhouse Gases"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "question": "What term describes the practice of growing crops in succession to maintain soil health?",
    "choices": ["Monoculture", "Crop Rotation", "Hydroponics", "Agroforestry"],
    "answer": "Crop Rotation"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "question": "Which phenomenon refers to the long-term transfer of water from the oceans to the land?",
    "choices": [
      "Evaporation",
      "Precipitation",
      "Condensation",
      "Hydrologic Cycle"
    ],
    "answer": "Hydrologic Cycle"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "question": "What type of pollution results from excessive nutrient runoff into water bodies?",
    "choices": [
      "Plastic Pollution",
      "Air Pollution",
      "Eutrophication",
      "Thermal Pollution"
    ],
    "answer": "Eutrophication"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "question": "What term is used for a species that is not native to a specific location and has a tendency to spread?",
    "choices": [
      "Endemic Species",
      "Keystone Species",
      "Invasive Species",
      "Indigenous Species"
    ],
    "answer": "Invasive Species"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "question": "Which gas contributes to both smog and acid rain?",
    "choices": [
      "Carbon Monoxide",
      "Nitrogen Oxide",
      "Sulfur Dioxide",
      "Methane"
    ],
    "answer": "Sulfur Dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "question": "What term describes the practice of managing natural resources to meet current and future human needs?",
    "choices": [
      "Conservation",
      "Sustainability",
      "Urbanization",
      "Deforestation"
    ],
    "answer": "Sustainability"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "question": "What phenomenon is marked by a significant reduction in sea ice due to climate change?",
    "choices": [
      "El Niño",
      "Polar Vortex",
      "Arctic Meltdown",
      "Ocean Acidification"
    ],
    "answer": "Arctic Meltdown"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "question": "What is the term for the maximum sustainable yield that an ecosystem can produce over time?",
    "choices": [
      "Ecological Capacity",
      "Biocapacity",
      "Carrying Capacity",
      "Biodiversity"
    ],
    "answer": "Biocapacity"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "question": "What term refers to the conversion of barren or agricultural land into a forest?",
    "choices": [
      "Deforestation",
      "Afforestation",
      "Reforestation",
      "Desertification"
    ],
    "answer": "Afforestation"
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "question": "Which layer of the atmosphere lies directly above the troposphere?",
    "choices": ["Stratosphere", "Mesosphere", "Thermosphere", "Exosphere"],
    "answer": "Stratosphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "question": "What is the process by which organisms break down organic material into simpler substances?",
    "choices": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Decomposition",
      "Fermentation",
      "Respiration"
    ],
    "answer": "Decomposition"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "question": "Which renewable energy source is derived directly from organic matter, such as plants and animal waste?",
    "choices": ["Solar Energy", "Wind Energy", "Biomass Energy", "Hydropower"],
    "answer": "Biomass Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "question": "What term describes the area where a freshwater stream or river merges with the ocean?",
    "choices": ["Estuary", "Delta", "Wetland", "Lagoon"],
    "answer": "Estuary"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "question": "What phenomenon leads to decreased fish populations due to changes in water temperature and chemistry?",
    "choices": [
      "Overfishing",
      "Coral Bleaching",
      "Ocean Acidification",
      "Eutrophication"
    ],
    "answer": "Ocean Acidification"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "question": "Which type of renewable energy involves using Earth's internal heat?",
    "choices": [
      "Solar Energy",
      "Wind Energy",
      "Geothermal Energy",
      "Hydropower"
    ],
    "answer": "Geothermal Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "question": "What is the process by which plants absorb sunlight and carbon dioxide to create food and oxygen?",
    "choices": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Respiration",
      "Transpiration",
      "Fermentation"
    ],
    "answer": "Photosynthesis"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "question": "What is the primary cause of urban heat islands?",
    "choices": [
      "Deforestation",
      "Industrial Pollution",
      "Increased Vehicle Use",
      "Concentration of Buildings and Pavement"
    ],
    "answer": "Concentration of Buildings and Pavement"
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "question": "Which form of waste management involves converting organic waste into soil conditioner?",
    "choices": ["Recycling", "Landfilling", "Composting", "Incineration"],
    "answer": "Composting"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "question": "What is the primary effect of eutrophication in aquatic ecosystems?",
    "choices": [
      "Increased Water Clarity",
      "Decreased Biodiversity",
      "Increased Fish Populations",
      "Oxygen Depletion"
    ],
    "answer": "Oxygen Depletion"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "question": "Which type of energy relies on capturing heat from within the Earth?",
    "choices": [
      "Solar Energy",
      "Wind Energy",
      "Nuclear Energy",
      "Geothermal Energy"
    ],
    "answer": "Geothermal Energy"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "question": "What is the term for the area where an ocean meets the land?",
    "choices": ["Coastline", "Continental Shelf", "Coral Reef", "Estuary"],
    "answer": "Coastline"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "What process is primarily responsible for the formation of fossil fuels?",
    "choices": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Carbon Sequestration",
      "Decomposition",
      "Sedimentation"
    ],
    "answer": "Sedimentation"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "question": "Which phenomenon occurs when the Earth's shadow falls on the Moon?",
    "choices": ["Solar Eclipse", "Lunar Eclipse", "Equinox", "Solstice"],
    "answer": "Lunar Eclipse"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "question": "What is the process by which green plants use sunlight to synthesize foods?",
    "choices": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Respiration",
      "Decomposition",
      "Fermentation"
    ],
    "answer": "Photosynthesis"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "question": "What term refers to the deliberate modification of Earth's environment through the addition or removal of species?",
    "choices": [
      "Biodiversity",
      "Ecology",
      "Conservation",
      "Ecosystem Engineering"
    ],
    "answer": "Ecosystem Engineering"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "question": "What is the term for the practice of growing crops and raising livestock for human use and consumption?",
    "choices": ["Horticulture", "Agriculture", "Aquaculture", "Silviculture"],
    "answer": "Agriculture"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "question": "Which term describes the movement of water through the Earth's hydrosphere?",
    "choices": [
      "Carbon Cycle",
      "Nitrogen Cycle",
      "Water Cycle",
      "Oxygen Cycle"
    ],
    "answer": "Water Cycle"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "question": "What phenomenon refers to the regular rise and fall of ocean levels?",
    "choices": ["Ocean Currents", "Tides", "El Niño", "Thermal Expansion"],
    "answer": "Tides"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "question": "What is the primary cause of soil salinization?",
    "choices": [
      "Overgrazing",
      "Deforestation",
      "Excessive Irrigation",
      "Industrial Pollution"
    ],
    "answer": "Excessive Irrigation"
  }
]
